{
    "subject": "resource/The_Elective_Affinities",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "The Elective Affinities (Italian: Le affinit\u00e0 elettive, French: Les affinit\u00e9s \u00e9lectives) is a 1996 Italian-French comedy film directed by Paolo and Vittorio Taviani. It was screened out of competition at the 1996 Cannes Film Festival.",
    "human_readable": "The Elective Affinities is a 1996 Italian-French comedy film directed by Paolo and Vittorio Taviani, which was screened out of competition at the 1996 Cannes Film Festival.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9379096031188965,
            "question": "At which film festival was 'The Elective Affinities' screened?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9102649688720703,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Elective Affinities'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8813018202781677,
            "question": "Is 'The Elective Affinities' a drama or a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8611850142478943,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Elective Affinities'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8548782467842102,
            "question": "Under what circumstances was 'The Elective Affinities' screened at Cannes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8414790630340576,
            "question": "In what year was 'The Elective Affinities' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7750164866447449,
            "question": "Besides Italy, what other country contributed to the making of 'The Elective Affinities'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6938051581382751,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the directors of 'The Elective Affinities'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6111562848091125,
            "question": "What is the primary language of 'The Elective Affinities'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41555291414260864,
            "question": "What type of film festival is Cannes known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Elective Affinities is a 1996 Italian-French comedy film directed by Paolo and Vittorio Taviani, which was screened out of competition at the 1996 Cannes Film Festival.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5158_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary language of 'The Elective Affinities'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5158_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of the directors of 'The Elective Affinities'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5158_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides Italy, what other country contributed to the making of 'The Elective Affinities'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5158_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5158_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided documents confirm that The Elective Affinities is a 1996 Italian-French comedy film directed by Paolo and Vittorio Taviani, which was screened out of competition at the 1996 Cannes Film Festival."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}